<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-18T21:36:47+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Sam’s Translations</title><subtitle>Hobbyist translator for Japanese Novels I like. Maybe there&apos;ll be mistakes, I&apos;m a work in progress.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">BG - Volume 6 Chapter 9: Tanaka Declears</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C9.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BG - Volume 6 Chapter 9: Tanaka Declears" /><published>2023-09-18T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C9</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C9.html"><![CDATA[<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter"><a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C8.html">Previous Chapter</a> | [Next Chapter]</h5>

<p>Tl: Sam</p>

<p>…</p>

<p>　Ten years had already passed since the birth of dungeons in the world. <br />
　During that time, dungeons had been thoroughly investigated by researchers from all over the world, and the magical elements and awakened people could be explained fairly scientifically.</p>

<p>　Even so, however, the key 『dungeon 』  was still largely unexplained.</p>

<p>　Where did they come from? What is their purpose? <br />
　Were they natural phenomena? Or were they artificially created?
　The more one investigates, the more one learns, and that is the biggest mystery of all. <br />
　Maki may have solved part of that mystery.
<!--more--></p>

<p>　If monsters came from a world different from ours, then dungeons would be no different. If we could prove that the dungeon came from a different world, many problems might be solved.</p>

<p>　If the world heard about this hypothesis, they would be very interested in it and make a fuss about it. <br />
　But I …… wasn’t so interested.</p>

<p>“Oh, really?” <br />
“Aren’t you rather low …… tension, Tanaka-kun?　Is it something that doesn’t matter to you?” <br />
“It’s not that I don’t care, but …… it won’t change what I’m going to do. <br />
“I’m curious. What exactly is it that you do?”</p>

<p>　Maki-san asked with interest. <br />
　A little embarrassed, I answer.</p>

<p>“It’s obvious. Slay the enemies that harm me and my loved ones. No matter where the dungeons and monsters come from, that won’t change.” <br />
“…… Hmmm.”</p>

<p>　Maki-san grinned as she looked at me happily.</p>

<p>“What is it?” <br />
“Even just three days can change a person; you’ve become quite reliable. Tachibana must be very proud.”</p>
<h6 id="tl-theres-a-chinese-idiom-here-the-original-story-is-a-chinese-traditional-story----it-is-based-on-the-story-of-a-young-chinese-man-who-surprised-everyone-by-learning--the-art-of-war--in-a-very-short-time-this-is-what-the-young-man-is-said-to-have-said-to-the-surprised-adults-around-him">(Tl: there’s a chinese idiom here. The original story is a Chinese traditional story.    It is based on the story of a young Chinese man who surprised everyone by learning &lt; the art of war &gt; in a very short time. This is what the young man is said to have said to the surprised adults around him.</h6>
<h6 id="男子三日会わざれば刮目して見よ-if-you-have-not-seen-the-young-man-for-more-than-three-days-the-next-time-you-see-him-look-at-him-carefully">・男子、三日会わざれば刮目して見よ. “If you have not seen the young man for more than three days, The next time you see him, look at him carefully.”</h6>
<h6 id="the-meaning-is-that-a-young-person-can-grow-into-a-different-person-in-three-days">The meaning is that a young person can grow into a different person in three days.)</h6>

<p>“……Thank you very much.”</p>

<p>　After complimenting me, Maki-san waved the smoke from her cigarette as if thinking a little. <br />
　Then she said something that I had never imagined.</p>

<p>“This is hardly known even within the government, but …… recently there have been signs of increased activity in the Imperial Palace dungeon.” <br />
What do you mean?”</p>

<p>　Maki’s sudden words startled me. <br />
　The dungeon directly below the Imperial Palace is one of the most difficult dungeons in the world, which was conquered by 300 searchers including me, Amatsuki and Dojima-san, and we managed to conquer it with the loss of more than 200 people.</p>

<p>　Seven years ago, we managed to deactivate the Imperial Palace dungeon after a desperate struggle. But if it were to be activated again, the world would be in an uproar. <br />
　The Imperial Palace dungeon is a unique type of dungeon. If it were to be activated, it would mean that a large number of monsters would appear in Tokyo once again.</p>

<p>“I miss it. The time I spent in that dungeon was one of the most exciting days of my life. I can still remember them vividly.”</p>

<p>　Yes, Maki was one of the members who dived with us in the dungeon just below the Imperial Palace. <br />
　She was not with us as a combatant, but as a special researcher to study the inside of the dungeon. However, she was more active than the other explorers, using weapons created by “magical science,” which combines magical elements and scientific technology, and contributed greatly to the dungeon invasion.</p>

<p>　Thanks to her power, Maki survived the dungeon just below the Imperial Palace and became one of the returnees, making her name even more well-known.
　The stigma of having once been involved in illegal research was erased, and she rose to the position of director of the Bureau of Magical Research.</p>

<p>Why did you give me such important information?” <br />
“I thought that if we ever had to conquer that dungeon again, you would be the key to it. If that’s the case, it’s good that you know. So that you won’t have any doubts when the time comes.”</p>

<p>　Maki-san said with a hint of sarcasm in her voice. <br />
　It’s true, that dungeon is where my mentor lost her life. I can say that it is a place of trauma for me. When the time comes, I might hesitate. But,</p>

<p>“If the time comes, I will go there. There are too many things that are important to me here in Tokyo.” <br />
“I’m glad to hear that. I look forward to the day when I can go there with you again.”</p>

<p>　Maki-san replied with a smile of genuine pleasure on her face. <br />
　I thanked her and headed home with Riri.</p>

<p>…..</p>

<p>Tl Note: We have another returnee enterring the chat, and she’s just going around raising flads here and there. I’m actually looking foward to the next chapter</p>

<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter-1"><a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C8.html">Previous Chapter</a> | [Next Chapter]</h5>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="black guild" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previous Chapter | [Next Chapter] Tl: Sam … 　Ten years had already passed since the birth of dungeons in the world. 　During that time, dungeons had been thoroughly investigated by researchers from all over the world, and the magical elements and awakened people could be explained fairly scientifically. 　Even so, however, the key 『dungeon 』 was still largely unexplained. 　Where did they come from? What is their purpose? 　Were they natural phenomena? Or were they artificially created? 　The more one investigates, the more one learns, and that is the biggest mystery of all. 　Maki may have solved part of that mystery.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BG - Volume 6 Chapter 8: Tanaka Is Told</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C8.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BG - Volume 6 Chapter 8: Tanaka Is Told" /><published>2023-09-16T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2023-09-16T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C8</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C8.html"><![CDATA[<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter"><a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C7.html">Previous Chapter</a> | <a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C9.html">Next Chapter</a></h5>

<p>Tl: Sam</p>

<p>…</p>

<p>“Come on!　It’s time for some fun, fun experimentation!”</p>

<p>　Maki operated a panel on the wall, and a mechanical platform appeared in the center of the room that seemed to have a variety of functions. There were several other futuristic devices in this room, the purpose of which was unknown. <br />
　I bet they all cost an eye-popping amount of money.</p>

<p>“Maki-san, you may examine Riri, but please don’t do anything …… violent, okay?” <br />
<!--more-->
“Of course not, Tanaka-kun. This is a precious and valuable offering that only one person could have. I’ll treat her with the utmost courtesy.”</p>

<p>　Maki-san said with a smile on her face.   <br />
　Well, I didn’t trust her. She’s the type of person who can’t see what’s going on around her when she’s in the heat of the moment. I kept a close watch on her.</p>

<p>“Come this way, young lady.” <br />
“Ri……”</p>

<p>　Riri was escorted to the platform and placed in the center of the room. <br />
　Riri was still a bit nervous, but she was obediently obeying Maki’s instructions. It seems that she faithfully complied with my prior request that she remain quiet during the inspection. I had to reward her later.</p>

<p>“Assistant-kun! Come help me!”</p>

<p>　Maki shouted as she fiddled with the machine. <br />
　Then, a figure appeared from the door leading to the back of the room.
It was a large fellow, about two meters tall. Dressed in a white coat, the figure’s shoulders are quite broad. On their face, they wore a mask with a pointed mouth…… a so-called plague mask. <br />
The eyes were covered with glass, so we couldn’t see the face. I could guess 　that he is a man from his body shape, but other than that, I had no idea what else he looked like.</p>

<p>　The man looked at me, bowed his head, and began to help me prepare for the experiment.</p>

<p>“Maki-san, this person…….” <br />
“He is my right-hand light arm, Sam, my first assistant. He’s a quiet guy, but an excellent assistant, well, don’t mind him.” (Tl: Tch, I’m happy I’m sharing names with someone in this novel, but I’m annoyed it’s a weirdo plague-plague docto doctor” <br />
“Haa …….”</p>

<p>　By the way, the woman who guided me here said she was the ‘ninth assistant’. She seemed pretty smart, too, but still ninth. So this big guy must be pretty smart. <br />
　However, this Sam or someone like him, I felt a “presence” different from that of an ordinary person. I wonder who he is.</p>

<p>“…… Dr. Kurosu. Preparations are complete. We can begin analysis at any time.” <br />
“I understand. Tanaka-kun, can you give us a cell sample before we begin?　As I recall, she can detach her own body, right?”
“Yes. Yes, I’ll ask her.”</p>

<p>　Riri often tears off her own body and feeds it to me. She doesn’t seem to feel any pain in the act.</p>

<p>“Riri, can you do it for me?” <br />
“Riri, …….”</p>

<p>　I asked, and Riri reluctantly tore off a piece of her own buttocks and handed it to me.
　Apparently, she didn’t want to tear off her own body part if I wasn’t going to eat it. I thanked Riri and placed it in the glass container in Maki’s hand.</p>

<p>“Hmmm, thanks for your cooperation, you two. This is a super valuable sample. Sam, please analyze it with the utmost care.” <br />
“Yes, ma’am.”</p>

<p>　Sam, the first assistant, placed Riri’s cells into the huge machine and operated the control panel. <br />
　Maki-san approaches Riri on the table and begins to examine her with various instruments.</p>

<p>“We’ll start with X-ray crystal structure analysis and optical spectral analysis……. Oh, and we can’t leave out the magnetic wavelength analysis, either. Sam, don’t forget to analyze the magiprotis.”(Tl: Wow, real science words) <br />
“Yes, I have already done that. Already done.” <br />
“Good.”</p>

<p>　The two of them were working in unison to find out more about Riri. <br />
　As Maki had declared at the beginning, she did not do anything that Riri did not want to do. On the contrary, she took care of Riri, feeding her and taking care of her physical condition. <br />
　I don’t know if it was out of kindness or if she was taking care of Lili’s physical condition for the sake of her research, but for the time being, nothing that I had been worried about seemed to be happening. <br />
　Riri, too, was relieved and curled up on her side.</p>

<p>“The analysis of the DNA structure is complete, Dr. Kurosu.” <br />
“Thank you. Let’s see…….” <br />
“No dungeon rock was found. I think it is safe to assume that it is an independent individual after all.” <br />
“That’s great. That’s great. My hypothesis was right after all.”</p>

<p>　Maki-san smiled happily. <br />
　Her face is completely that of an evil scientist. It was hard to believe that she was from the government side.</p>

<p>“The cell culture is going well…… and this is about the only thing we can examine in the living body right now.”</p>

<p>　Maki-san, who had been examining her for a while, said this and released Riri. <br />
　As I approached, Riri jumped at me.</p>

<p>“Riri!” <br />
“Oops, watch out. You did a good job.”</p>

<p>　I caught Riri and patted her head to thank her for her hard work. I pat her on the head and thank her for her effort.</p>

<p>“Thanks to you, Tanaka, I was able to do some good research today. That’s a big step forward.”</p>

<p>　Maki-san, perhaps exhausted from the exertion of her work, approached me, dizzy. <br />
　However, the look in her eyes was a little scary.</p>

<p>“He was saying that our hypothesis was correct. Did you find out something important?” <br />
“Aah. It is known that monsters born in dungeons usually have a DNA structure similar to that of the dungeon.” <br />
“The same DNA as in the dungeon?” <br />
“Yes. Each dungeon has its own DNA, and the monster born in the dungeon inherits a part of that DNA. Just like a parent and its child.” <br />
“…… Wait a minute. Does that mean dungeons are “living things”?” <br />
“Yes and no. Dungeons are still a mystery to us.”</p>

<p>　Maki-san laughs happily. <br />
　If she doesn’t know, then no one can answer the question yet.</p>

<p>“Well, let’s just assume that the DNA of the dungeon is engraved in the monster. And that DNA is the proof that the dungeon binds the monster tightly. As you know, when the dungeon is destroyed, the monsters themselves die in a chain reaction.”</p>

<p>　I know that too. <br />
　Breaking a dungeon not only stops the creation of more monsters, it also defeats the monsters that have already been created.</p>

<p>“Researchers believe that when a dungeon is broken, this DNA causes monsters to die. We call the DNA the ‘dungeon lock,’ the binding that the labyrinth puts on the monster. This is something that every monster born from the dungeon can have. But……”</p>

<p>　Maki looked at Riri in my hand.</p>

<p>“That child does not have dungeon lock. In other words, …… that child is not bound to the dungeon. It is a completely independent life form.”</p>

<p>　Hearing this, Riri tilts her head, “Ri? Lili tilted her head. <br />
　She probably doesn’t know that she is a special being.</p>

<p>“Do you understand, Tanaka-kun? Do you know how great this is? Until now, it was thought that monsters could only be born in dungeons. But it was different. The child proved that monsters can exist on their own.”</p>

<p>　Maki says excitedly. <br />
　Riri’s existence certainly proves that it is possible for monsters to be born and live without relying on dungeons.</p>

<p>“I think of it this way. I believe that dungeons only create beings that are similar to monsters. So, the original monster must live somewhere.　At least, there is no such thing on earth. In other words ……”</p>

<p>　Maki-san looked me in the eye and spoke of her hypothesis.</p>

<p>“They live in a different dimension, a different world than here. That’s where the dungeons and magical elements came from.”</p>

<p>Tl Note: Just gave our site a new make over, coutsey a member Dave. You can probably find him in the comments. I’m done with my exams, but I didn’t get a holiday so I’m stuck doing Engineering Drawing assignments, the author releases really slowly though, and that leavs me with soome free time. I’m taking novel reccomendations in the discord server. Aaaaand before I forget, I have 2 announcements</p>

<ul>
  <li>My Birthday is next friday, I wonder how I’ll spend it, but I have class, so I won’t have much time</li>
  <li>I’m thinking of posting My original novel, I’ve had it throuout this year, and I think I should share it. I cuuently have only 8 chapters down and I’m almost done with the first arc/volume. It’ll also be donation based, so If you really wwant a new chapter so much, you could go on my patreon and ask for it. I was originally going to make it 2nd tier patren members only (You can check my patreon and you’ll see), but a friend motivated me to post it out for free.</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter-1"><a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C7.html">Previous Chapter</a> | <a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C9.html">Next Chapter</a></h5>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="black guild" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previous Chapter | Next Chapter Tl: Sam … “Come on!　It’s time for some fun, fun experimentation!” 　Maki operated a panel on the wall, and a mechanical platform appeared in the center of the room that seemed to have a variety of functions. There were several other futuristic devices in this room, the purpose of which was unknown. 　I bet they all cost an eye-popping amount of money. “Maki-san, you may examine Riri, but please don’t do anything …… violent, okay?”]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BG - Volume 6 Chapter 7: Tanaka Is Attacked</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C7.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BG - Volume 6 Chapter 7: Tanaka Is Attacked" /><published>2023-09-13T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C7</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C7.html"><![CDATA[<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter"><a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C6.html">Previous Chapter</a> | <a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C8.html">Next Chapter</a></h5>

<p>Tl: Sam</p>

<p>…</p>

<p>　Director of the Bureau of Magical Research, Kurosu Maki. <br />
　If I had to sum her up in one word, it would be “eccentric”.</p>

<p>　She loves research so much that she has no interest in anything else. The fact that she wears only a white coat on her upper body probably stems from her lack of interest in clothing.  <br />
　She only eats solid, complete nutritional food, and the sleep she takes is minimal. She has no desire for money or to be popular with the opposite sex.
<!--more--></p>

<p>　She just wants to be free to do the research she is interested in, and that is all she wants.</p>

<p>“Well, sit down, Tanaka-kun. Let’s welcome you.”</p>

<p>　Maki-san sat down on the desk and put his feet on the back of the chair.  <br />
　It was very ill-mannered, but this was her normal behavior. If I had to point out every single thing, there would be no end to it. It would be nonsense to point out her manners and civility.</p>

<p>“I am surprised that you are still doing your research under the government. I thought you would leave as soon as possible.” <br />
“Hey, hey, hey, what do you think I am?　I’m just a quiet dog with a collar on. I won’t do anything that will bother you.”</p>

<p>　Maki said with a hearty laugh. <br />
　Well, I don’t trust her. After all, this person’s background is unusual.</p>

<p>　Even as a junior high school student, she was already as knowledgeable as an adult researcher and was sought out by various research institutes. It was amazing that she was sometimes invited to famous universities overseas.</p>

<p>　Maki’s career as a researcher was going smoothly, but a turning point came when she was nineteen years old. <br />
　It was the advent of the dungeon. With a personality of curiosity wearing a white coat, Maki was fascinated by the charms of dungeons. <br />
At first, Maki was doing research at a public institution, but ethical and safety concerns made it difficult to get approval for her experiments. Especially when it came to experiments on human subjects.</p>

<p>　Therefore, Maki-san disappeared from the public eye and began to conduct illegal experiments behind the scenes. There are many rich people interested in dungeon research, so she would have had no trouble finding funding sponsors.</p>

<p>　For the next few years or so, Maki-san continued her research as she pleased, but a second turning point came. It was an investigation led by Dojima-san to force the Monster Subjugation Bureau to take action. <br />
　Illegal research institutions were all shut down, and Maki was detained in the process. <br />
　Normally, she would have been arrested, but Dojima-san hired her on the condition that she would not engage in such illegal activities in the future and that she would return all the results of her research to the government.</p>

<p>　Naturally, the government and the media were all over him about it, but he brushed it off. <br />
　I thought it was a mess, but as it turns out, thanks to Maki-san, Japan is one step ahead of other countries in dungeon research. <br />
　It is also thanks to Maki-san that we are able to manage even though there are more dungeons than in other countries.</p>

<p>“I would love to do five or six inhumane experiments on human beings. I’ve thought about getting out of here and going back into the underground. But…… the current situation is not so bad. It’s a great way to get a little extra money for my research, and I don’t have to worry about Dojima-san’s eyes on me.”</p>

<p>　Maki-san laughed. <br />
　I don’t want you to say that you’ve thought about betraying us because it’s bad for my heart.</p>

<p>“By the way, Maki-san, I was wondering about your arm…….” <br />
“Oh, this one.”</p>

<p>　I pointed out, and Maki-san put her right arm out in front of her. <br />
　Her right arm was a mechanical arm from the elbow to the tip. It looks like the main character in a famous shounen manga(Tl: Probably Edward Elric from FMA). When I met her before, it must have been a normal arm, but I wondered if she had opened the door to truth through too much research.(Tl: Another FMA reference)</p>

<p>“Isn’t this cool?　It’s useful, you know.”</p>

<p>　Maki-san said, and a blue light gushed out from the tip of her index finger. She lit a cigarette in her mouth with the light and took a sigh of relief. <br />
　Obviously, the chemicals and machines here are supposed to be non-smoking, I wonder if it’s okay. Well, the director here smokes, so why should I bother to mention it?</p>

<p>“I don’t think it’s cool, rather, What the hell happened to your arm?” <br />
“It’s a noble sacrifice. Don’t worry about it.”</p>

<p>　Maki-san brushed it off with that. <br />
　I was wondering if I should ask her about it, but if she didn’t want to tell me, I didn’t have to ask.</p>

<p>　As I was thinking this, I noticed Maki-san sitting at her desk, looking at me and fidgeting. I saw her cheeks were slightly reddish.</p>

<p>“What’s wrong?”
“I thought it’s time to…… you know.”
“About time?”
“I want you to show me that thing you’re holding. I can’t take it anymore!””</p>

<p>　Maki-san jumped down from the desk and approached me.
　Her agile movements startled me. I was surprised. Maki-san is an awakened person herself, so her physical abilities are extremely high.</p>

<p>“Maki-san!” <br />
Tanaka-kun, show me the Shogos-kun that you….. you have with you!” <br />
“Eeh?”</p>

<p>　As I let out a stupid voice, Riri came out of my breast pocket and looked at me. I’m not sure what to say. I had forgotten that I had come here to show you Riri. <br />
　There are no other monsters friendly to humans, except for Riri, so it is only natural that Maki-san is interested in her. <br />
　Riri’s eyes fluttered in surprise. Naturally, her eyes met those of Maki-san, who was standing right in front of me.</p>

<p>　Maki’s expression hardened for a moment, and then she smiled.</p>

<p>“Oh, well, well, well. It’s so nice to finally meet you, cutie. I’ve been waiting for the day I’d meet you for ages.”</p>

<p>　At the sound of her mousy voice and gaze, Riri seemed to pull back a little, “Riri…….” <br />
　It was indeed Maki-san who could make Riri, who was always so easy-going, to pull away.</p>

<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter-1"><a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C6.html">Previous Chapter</a> | <a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C8.html">Next Chapter</a></h5>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="black guild" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previous Chapter | Next Chapter Tl: Sam … 　Director of the Bureau of Magical Research, Kurosu Maki. 　If I had to sum her up in one word, it would be “eccentric”. 　She loves research so much that she has no interest in anything else. The fact that she wears only a white coat on her upper body probably stems from her lack of interest in clothing. 　She only eats solid, complete nutritional food, and the sleep she takes is minimal. She has no desire for money or to be popular with the opposite sex.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">SC - Volume 2 Chapter 13: Heroic Tale</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C13.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="SC - Volume 2 Chapter 13: Heroic Tale" /><published>2023-09-13T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C13</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C13.html"><![CDATA[<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter"><a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C12.html">Previous Chapter</a> | [Next Chapter]</h5>

<p>Tl: Sam</p>

<p>…</p>

<p>“I’m sorry to bother you.”</p>

<p>“Welcome.”</p>

<p>　When I entered the house, I was greeted by a beastman.</p>

<p>　Like Luna, he had white hair. He was about sixty years old. He looked quite old.</p>

<p>“My name is Tungul. Please have a seat here.”</p>

<p>　I sat down on the cushion placed in front of him as Mr. Tungul urged me.
<!--more--></p>

<p>　The beastmen in Seven Knights Online were a bit rough around the edges, but this man was quite calm and rational. It is dangerous to make assumptions based on in-game impressions.</p>

<p>“First of all, let me thank you. Thank you for saving Luna.”</p>

<p>　Tungul-san bowed deeply.</p>

<p>　When I sent people back to their villages, I often sent them back with me, but Luna said she could go home by herself and quickly left.</p>

<p>“I’ve been meaning to thank you for a long time, but at thihs age, my legs and back are not good enough to go out there. I am sorry.”</p>

<p>“No, no, not at all. I did what I had to do.”</p>

<p>“Oh, Luna is right, you are a generous man. Thank you, thank you…….”</p>

<p>　Tungul rubbed his hands together and repeated his words.</p>

<p>　Now that the atmosphere has warmed up a bit, let’s get down to business.</p>

<p>“I heard from Luna that this village is now plagued by orcs.”</p>

<p>“…… Yes. It is a shame that the proud White Wolf Tribe should be plagued by such creatures.”</p>

<p>　The white wolf tribe is probably the name of their clan.</p>

<p>　The ears and tail certainly resemble wolves.</p>

<p>“Have orcs lived nearby before?”</p>

<p>“No, they used to live far away from this village. However, due to a period of time when there was no rain, it seems that they had trouble finding food, so they moved here…….”</p>

<p>　I see. So it wasn’t only around the village of Jimari that was in need of food.</p>

<p>　However, if that is the reason, there seems to be little hope for the orcs to return to where they came from. No wonder they are worried.</p>

<p>“It would be better if they simply stayed in the same habitat area, but…… they are planning to attack our village. They are tough and numerous. There is no chance we can win.”</p>

<p>　Tungul said with a dark look on his face.</p>

<p>　I saw a lot of old people and children in the village. If they all ran away together, they would become a target. If we can’t reconcile, then we have no choice but to fight.</p>

<p>“Did you talk to the orcs?”</p>

<p>“They can speak, but other than that, they are no better than monsters. They see us only as prey.”</p>

<p>“I see. So we have no choice but to fight.”</p>

<p>“Yes…….”</p>

<p>　I had a general idea of what was going on.</p>

<p>　The orcs were evil monsters that harmed people in Seven Knights Online, but that doesn’t seem to have changed in this world either.</p>

<p>　If that’s the case, then I can defeat them with peace of mind.</p>

<p>“Thank you for speaking with us.”</p>

<p>“Oh, are you leaving already?”</p>

<p>“Yes, I think it would be better to take action as soon as possible.”</p>

<p>　Tungul-san tilted his head at my words.</p>

<p>“What do you mean?”</p>

<p>“I will take care of the orcs. Please wait and rest assured.”</p>

<p>Tl: Sam</p>

<p>…</p>

<p>　After talking with the village head, I left the house.</p>

<p>　The sun is starting to set a little. I decided to take it easy today and start work tomorrow.</p>

<p>“Now, where are Shea and the others?”</p>

<p>　I walked through the village looking for them.</p>

<p>　hm? I can’t help but feel someone’s eyes on me.</p>

<p>　It is true that I felt a lot of stares when I came to the village. However, it felt a little different from the way I felt at that time. At that time, I felt a strong sense of caution and hostility, but I don’t feel so bad about this now.</p>

<p>　On the contrary, I sometimes even felt a sense of respect. What is going on?</p>

<p>”—- and at that time, Dyle-sama took a swing at the bad guys!　He rescued those who were being held captive brilliantly!”</p>

<p>　I heard a familiar voice.</p>

<p>　I turned toward it and found that Shea was speaking, to a crowd of beastmen.　Or was it a speech?</p>

<p>“…… what are you doing?”</p>

<p>　I approached the place with a bad premonition.</p>

<p>　Shea was talking about the time I defeated the bandits. I didn’t tell her how I fought the bandits, so she probably heard it from Luna.</p>

<p>　Shea’s storytelling was so impassioned that I couldn’t help but listen in.</p>

<p>　The beasts, hungry for entertainment, were listening intently, and whenever Shea spoke passionately, they would shout, “Oh,” or “Wow! and “Wow!</p>

<p>　Could this be the reason why they were staring at me earlier?</p>

<p>　If they hear me talk like this, they might start to admire me like a character in a story. Or rather, they are probably already in love with me.</p>

<p>　I was wondering what was wrong with me,</p>

<p>”—-The evil bandits who tormented the people were successfully defeated. By the hand of Dyle-sama who is there!</p>

<p>“Yes.”</p>

<p>　The eyes of the beastmen who had been listening turned to me all at once.</p>

<p>　And then they all rushed toward me at once.</p>

<p>“You were great, weren’t you?　I respected you!”</p>

<p>“Yawn, yawn!”</p>

<p>“What kind of king are you?　Tell me!”</p>

<p>“Hey, hey Just calm down”</p>

<p>　The beastmen were making me squirm.</p>

<p>　I was finally released and set free after dark.</p>

<p>◇　◇　◇</p>

<p>“……Fu, I’m tired.”</p>

<p>　Night.</p>

<p>We were staying in the cabin where Luna usually lives.</p>

<p>　It’s a small hut, so it was cramped for three people to sleep in, but it’s nice to have something like this once in a while.</p>

<p>　By the way, Luna’s parents had already passed away. So she often wandered around the forest alone, and was unluckily caught by the bandits.</p>

<p>“Now, let me ask you something, Shea. Why did you do that?”</p>

<p>　Shea looked like she had done her job.</p>

<p>　I was in a lot of trouble because of it. I’d like to complain about it.</p>

<p>“I had, of course, been telling everyone in the village how wonderful Dyle-sama was. He told us to be on our guard. If that was the case, I thought it would be quicker and more effective to tell them about the saga of Dyle than to show them how well Luna and I got along.”</p>

<p>“I see.”</p>

<p>　I did ask her to lower everyone’s guard, but that was just a ploy.</p>

<p>　I just wanted to make sure that Shea and Luna relaxed.</p>

<p>“I’m sure Luna wasn’t busy either, was she?”</p>

<p>“I was not.  Shea’s story was interesting, and I wanted to hear more.”</p>

<p>“Is that so….”</p>

<p>　Looked like she was enjoying it more than I thought.</p>

<p>　I feel like she did something unnecessary, but it is also true that the beastmen liked Shea because of her actions.</p>

<p>I went from being a troublesome outsider to being treated like a hero all at once. - I’m not sure what to make of that.</p>

<p>　The first time I saw her, I was wondering whether I should scold her or not, when all of a sudden, she became very sad and her eyes started to get all moist.</p>

<p>“Did I …… do something unnecessary?　I am so sorry …….”(Tl: The Devil, I say)</p>

<p>　Shea said in a voice that sounded as if she was about to start crying.</p>

<p>　Wait, I didn’t expect this to happen. I had to comfort her in a hurry!</p>

<p>“No, it’s not like that, Shea!　I couldn’t come up with such a great plan. I’m so lucky to have such a brilliant person in my life!”</p>

<p>“Do you really think so, ……?”</p>

<p>“Ah! Of course!”</p>

<p>　Fu, It worked out somehow.</p>

<p>“Um, so Dyle-sama. How did your discussion with the village chief go?”</p>

<p>“Oh, about the orcs. It seems to be more serious than I thought, and I think it’s best to settle it as soon as possible. I want you two to get started as soon as tomorrow morning.”</p>

<p>　When I asked this, Shea and Luna nodded cockily without hesitation.</p>

<p>“Of course. Anything you need, we’re at your service.”</p>

<p>“I’ll do my best.”</p>

<p>“Thank you, both of you. I’m counting on you.”</p>

<p>　I went to bed with my two reliable allies.</p>

<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter-1"><a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C12.html">Previous Chapter</a> | [Next Chapter]</h5>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="silver castle" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previous Chapter | [Next Chapter] Tl: Sam … “I’m sorry to bother you.” “Welcome.” 　When I entered the house, I was greeted by a beastman. 　Like Luna, he had white hair. He was about sixty years old. He looked quite old. “My name is Tungul. Please have a seat here.” 　I sat down on the cushion placed in front of him as Mr. Tungul urged me.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">SC - Volume 2 Chapter 12: Unforseen Circumstances</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C12.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="SC - Volume 2 Chapter 12: Unforseen Circumstances" /><published>2023-09-11T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C12</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C12.html"><![CDATA[<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter"><a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C11.html">Previous Chapter</a> | <a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C13.html">Next Chapter</a></h5>

<p>Tl: Sam</p>

<p>…</p>

<p>“I’m sorry to bother you.”</p>

<p>“Welcome.”</p>

<p>　When I entered the house, I was greeted by a beastman.</p>

<p>　Like Luna, he had white hair. He was about sixty years old. He looked quite old.</p>

<p>“My name is Tungul. Please have a seat here.”</p>

<p>　I sat down on the cushion placed in front of him as Mr. Tungul urged me.</p>

<p>　The beastmen in Seven Knights Online were a bit rough around the edges, but this man was quite calm and rational. It is dangerous to make assumptions based on in-game impressions.
<!--more--></p>

<p>“First of all, let me thank you. Thank you for saving Luna.”</p>

<p>　Tungul-san bowed deeply.</p>

<p>　When I sent people back to their villages, I often sent them back with me, but Luna said she could go home by herself and quickly left.</p>

<p>“I’ve been meaning to thank you for a long time, but at thihs age, my legs and back are not good enough to go out there. I am sorry.”</p>

<p>“No, no, not at all. I did what I had to do.”</p>

<p>“Oh, Luna is right, you are a generous man. Thank you, thank you…….”</p>

<p>　Tungul rubbed his hands together and repeated his words.</p>

<p>　Now that the atmosphere has warmed up a bit, let’s get down to business.</p>

<p>“I heard from Luna that this village is now plagued by orcs.”</p>

<p>“…… Yes. It is a shame that the proud White Wolf Tribe should be plagued by such creatures.”</p>

<p>　The white wolf tribe is probably the name of their clan.</p>

<p>　The ears and tail certainly resemble wolves.</p>

<p>“Have orcs lived nearby before?”</p>

<p>“No, they used to live far away from this village. However, due to a period of time when there was no rain, it seems that they had trouble finding food, so they moved here…….”</p>

<p>　I see. So it wasn’t only around the village of Jimari that was in need of food.</p>

<p>　However, if that is the reason, there seems to be little hope for the orcs to return to where they came from. No wonder they are worried.</p>

<p>“It would be better if they simply stayed in the same habitat area, but…… they are planning to attack our village. They are tough and numerous. There is no chance we can win.”</p>

<p>　Tungul said with a dark look on his face.</p>

<p>　I saw a lot of old people and children in the village. If they all ran away together, they would become a target. If we can’t reconcile, then we have no choice but to fight.</p>

<p>“Did you talk to the orcs?”</p>

<p>“They can speak, but other than that, they are no better than monsters. They see us only as prey.”</p>

<p>“I see. So we have no choice but to fight.”</p>

<p>“Yes…….”</p>

<p>　I had a general idea of what was going on.</p>

<p>　The orcs were evil monsters that harmed people in Seven Knights Online, but that doesn’t seem to have changed in this world either.</p>

<p>　If that’s the case, then I can defeat them with peace of mind.</p>

<p>“Thank you for speaking with us.”</p>

<p>“Oh, are you leaving already?”</p>

<p>“Yes, I think it would be better to take action as soon as possible.”</p>

<p>　Tungul-san tilted his head at my words.</p>

<p>“What do you mean?”</p>

<p>“I will take care of the orcs. Please wait and rest assured.”</p>

<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter-1"><a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C11.html">Previous Chapter</a> | <a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C13.html">Next Chapter</a></h5>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="silver castle" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previous Chapter | Next Chapter Tl: Sam … “I’m sorry to bother you.” “Welcome.” 　When I entered the house, I was greeted by a beastman. 　Like Luna, he had white hair. He was about sixty years old. He looked quite old. “My name is Tungul. Please have a seat here.” 　I sat down on the cushion placed in front of him as Mr. Tungul urged me. 　The beastmen in Seven Knights Online were a bit rough around the edges, but this man was quite calm and rational. It is dangerous to make assumptions based on in-game impressions.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">SC - Volume 2 Chapter 11: White Wolf Village</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C11.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="SC - Volume 2 Chapter 11: White Wolf Village" /><published>2023-09-10T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C11</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C11.html"><![CDATA[<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter"><a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C10.html">Previous Chapter</a> | <a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C12.html">Next Chapter</a></h5>

<p>Tl: Sam</p>

<p>…</p>

<p>—- and well, this happened before.</p>

<p>　I’ve thought about it a lot since then, and I’ve come to the conclusion that if I want to make someone stronger first, it should be Shea.</p>

<p>　She is a smart girl, but physically she is an ordinary girl. (Tl:  He wants to give power to the devil)</p>

<p>　She seemed to be working a lot for me recently in places I didn’t even know existed, and that seems to have caused her to become fatigued.
<!--more--></p>

<p>　She wouldn’t stop even if I told her that she didn’t have to work so hard. Then I thought it would be good to have a body that would not get tired no matter how much she moves. If she became stronger, she would be able to fight off bandits and other attackers again.</p>

<p>“……We’re almost there.”</p>

<p>　Luna, the beastman walking in the lead, said so.</p>

<p>　Luna and Shea and I were walking through a thick forest.</p>

<p>　The destination was the village where Luna lives. She said we were almost there, but there was no sign of people around us and there was no road. It didn’t seem like there was a village at all.</p>

<p>“We have arrived. That’s the village of Lulu. That’s where I live.”</p>

<p>　Luna pointed in the direction of the village, and sure enough, there it was.</p>

<p>　But it wasn’t like a human village at all. Usually in human villages, trees are cut down and houses are built, but in their village, trees were used as they are and used as houses.</p>

<p>Of course, some trees were cut down to make open spaces, but this was minimal. They were like natives living in the jungle.</p>

<p>“Come on.”</p>

<p>　I followed Luna into the village.</p>

<p>　It must have been the first time for a human being to come to this village. The beastmen living in the village were staring at us. The children were simply curious, while the adults were wary.</p>

<p>　It was only natural that they would be wary of someone like me in a heavy armor.</p>

<p>　While I was thinking about this, Luna’s footsteps stopped in front of a house.</p>

<p>　It was a simple house made of wood. It was bigger than the other houses, so I wondered if someone important lived there.</p>

<p>“Wait a minute.”</p>

<p>　Luna entered the house saying so.</p>

<p>　After about five minutes of waiting, Luna came out of the house.</p>

<p>“The village chief says he is going to see Dyle-sama. Please do so.”</p>

<p>“I see, it was the village chief’s house. Well…… I’m going to talk to the village chief alone, so I want you two to kill some time at random. I don’t have plans to do anything in particular today, so you can go ahead and play.”</p>

<p>“Eh, but……”</p>

<p>　Shea showed no appreciation for my suggestion.</p>

<p>　Even when we were in the village of Jimari, she was more interested in helping me than playing with me. I’m happy that you want to be of help to me, but it’s also important to have fun once in a while.</p>

<p>　Even though she made a new friend in Luna. I still don’t know what she’s talking about, but I often see them enjoying themselves in the village these days.</p>

<p>　Well, what should I do?</p>

<p>　I could at least have a discussion with the village chief by myself, so I wanted Shea to play and relax.</p>

<p>　But if I told her honestly, she wouldn’t be convinced. I would have to come up with some kind of reason.</p>

<p>“Okay, Shea, I’ll give you a job.”</p>

<p>“Yes!　Anything!”</p>

<p>“We are still under the suspicion of the people of this village, and that’s not good.”</p>

<p>“Yes, it is.”</p>

<p>“There. I want you to play nice with Luna and let people know that we are safe and not hostile. I can’t do it this way. I can only ask Shea, who is still very young and is not very intimidating.”</p>

<p>“Only I can …… do this!　I understand, I’ll take care of it!”</p>

<p>　Shea replied with full of motivation.</p>

<p>　Well, I managed to persuade her.</p>

<p>　But even though it was just an idea, it’s a good one, isn’t it?　I feel it’s much more effective than my various other moves.</p>

<p>“Well then, I’ll be counting on you, Shea.”</p>

<p>“Yes!　Plese leave it to me!”</p>

<p>　Leaving Shea in a state of enthusiasm and Luna in a state of blank amazement, I went into the village headman’s house.</p>

<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter-1"><a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C10.html">Previous Chapter</a> | <a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C12.html">Next Chapter</a></h5>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="silver castle" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previous Chapter | Next Chapter Tl: Sam … —- and well, this happened before. 　I’ve thought about it a lot since then, and I’ve come to the conclusion that if I want to make someone stronger first, it should be Shea. 　She is a smart girl, but physically she is an ordinary girl. (Tl: He wants to give power to the devil) 　She seemed to be working a lot for me recently in places I didn’t even know existed, and that seems to have caused her to become fatigued.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BG - Volume 6 Chapter 6: Tanaka Goes To The Magic Lab</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C6.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BG - Volume 6 Chapter 6: Tanaka Goes To The Magic Lab" /><published>2023-09-08T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C6</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C6.html"><![CDATA[<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter"><a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C5.html">Previous Chapter</a> | <a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C7.html">Next Chapter</a></h5>

<p>Tl: Sam</p>

<p>…</p>

<p>“……It’s been a long time since I’ve been here.”</p>

<p>　I muttered to myself as I looked at the building standing in front of me. The large building on the side looks like a general hospital. <br />
　  In this building, various special events related to dungeons, such as monsters, magical element, and magic, are researched.
<!--more--></p>

<p>　Magic element is attracting worldwide attention as a new type of energy. <br />
　High concentrations of magical element have adverse effects on living creatures, but it does not produce harmful smoke. If it is handled properly, it will become the strongest clean energy.</p>

<p>　Japan’s Magick Research Bureau is also doing its best to tackle this problem, and it seems to be producing a certain amount of results. <br />
　The person who has contributed to this is the genius scientist I am about to meet, Maki Kurosu-san.</p>

<p>“Maki-san is also a bit of an oddball. …… I wonder if this souvenir will be enough.”</p>

<p>　I muttered to myself as I looked at the sweet-looking confectionery I had bought in Shinjuku. <br />
　Well, there’s no point in being anxious. I took a deep breath and went into the Magic Research Bureau.</p>

<p>　The interior was as clean and white as it had been in the past. The center of the building is a stairwell, with glass elevators going back and forth between the upper and lower floors. <br />
　In the first section, people in white coats were hurriedly moving around, and there was a faint smell of chemicals. <br />
　I went to the reception desk and told them what I had come for. A slender woman in a white coat soon arrived. She looks intelligent and wears glasses. This is probably the first time we have met.</p>

<p>“Nice to meet you, Tanaka-sama. Thank you for coming to see me. My name is Akira Fukami, Dr. Kurosu’s ninth assistant. Pleased to meet you.”</p>

<p>　The woman who introduced herself as Fukami bowed her head to me. <br />
　She bowed her head to me, her face was inorganic and her expression did not change, though her gesture was polite. I couldn’t quite figure out what she was thinking.</p>

<p>“Thank you very much for your kind attention. My name is Makoto Tanaka. , I’m here to see Maki-san…… um, Director Kurosu.” <br />
“Yes. Dr. Kurosu is waiting for you in the back. Please come this way and I will show you around.”</p>

<p>　I followed behind Fukami-san as she walked with her heels clacking. <br />
　I look around as I walk. I hear what sounds like explosions from time to time, but I wonder what kind of research they are doing.　I wonder what kind of research they’re doing. I’m sure most of what I hear I don’t understand.</p>

<p>“Are you nervous?” <br />
“What?”</p>

<p>　Fukami-san noticed my fidgeting and turned around to ask me.</p>

<p>“Well…… yes. A little.” <br />
“On the first floor, we mainly study unknown materials collected in the dungeon. Ores, plants, and monster materials are among them. They are analyzed with state-of-the-art equipment and discussed in terms of how they can be useful to mankind.”</p>

<p>　With that, Fukami pushed the elevator button and got in. <br />
　I followed her lead and entered the elevator.</p>

<p>“On the second floor, we are doing basic research on magical element and a little bit on the phenomenon of magic. We have a separate Magic Analysis Bureau, so we leave the analysis of magic to them.” <br />
“I see.”</p>

<p>　These people are researchers by nature. <br />
　Actual magic is very contained and may be of little interest to them. Perhaps they’re more interested in unknown substances and new uses for magic essence.</p>

<p>“On the third floor, the applied research of magical elements…… is mainly concerned with their effects on the human body. This includes observation of changes in the structure of the human body when a person becomes awakened, and research on the mechanism of the increase or decrease of the allowable amount of magical element. The fourth floor is for more advanced research on magical element. And the fifth floor is …….”</p>

<p>　The elevator arrived at the top floor with a ding. <br />
　On the only floor that is not vaulted, there was a heavy metal door that looks like a safe.</p>

<p>“The fifth floor is Dr. Kurosu’s private research space. Only a limited number of people are allowed on this floor, and even assistants such as myself are not allowed to enter freely.”</p>

<p>　Fukami-san began fiddling with the terminal next to the metal door. <br />
　He punched in a PIN number, had his card key authenticated, and then went through the retina authentication process ……. It was quite strict.</p>

<p>“It’s very secure” <br />
“Dr. Kurosu is the greatest brain of Japan, the greatest treasure. It is only natural that it should be this strict.” <br />
“I see…….”</p>

<p>　It seems that Fukami-san has a great deal of respect for Maki-san. At a level that can be called worship. <br />
　Maybe most of the people who work here are like that. As I was thinking this, Fukami-san spoke into the microphone. It seems that he has connected with the inside.</p>

<p>“Dr. Kurosu. I have brought Makoto Tanaka-sama with me.”</p>

<p>　When Fukami-san said this into the microphone, it was answered only with a short “Okay,” and the metal door started to open. <br />
　The walls of this floor seem to be quite thick. A bomb wouldn’t be enough to break through. With such tight security, it is unlikely that anyone will try to break into this room.</p>

<p>“Please come in.”</p>

<p>　I walk behind Fukami-san and enter the room. <br />
　Then, a person welcomes us.</p>

<p>“Hello, Tanaka-kun, it’s been a while.”</p>

<p>　The person appeared, fluttering a white coat. <br />
　Tall and slender, with black-rimmed glasses. WIth an unlit cigarette in mouth and long black hair, messily tied back with a hair elastic. <br />
　What was most striking was the upper body. Maki-san was wearing a white lab coat directly on her skin, with nothing else on her upper body. It is not a naked apron, but a naked lab coat. In addition, her chest and navel are exposed because it is not buttoned up.</p>

<p>　If it were a man, it would not be such a problem, but…… Maki-san is a woman. Maki-san’s face is also well-shaped, and she is very popular among women.</p>

<p>“I’m sorry it’s been so long, Maki-san. You are still dressed like that…….” <br />
“The white coat is the most excellent garment ever developed by man. If you have this, you don’t need any other clothes. I really want to take off the bothersome undergarments as well…… but Dojima-san forbids me to do so. The world of mankind is a very cramped place.”</p>

<p>　The owner of the strongest brain, the pride of Japan, spoke languidly of her desire to be exposed.</p>

<p>….</p>

<p>Tl Note: Tanaka really knows no normal people older than him.</p>

<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter-1"><a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C5.html">Previous Chapter</a> | <a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C7.html">Next Chapter</a></h5>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="black guild" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previous Chapter | Next Chapter Tl: Sam … “……It’s been a long time since I’ve been here.” 　I muttered to myself as I looked at the building standing in front of me. The large building on the side looks like a general hospital. 　 In this building, various special events related to dungeons, such as monsters, magical element, and magic, are researched.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">SC - Volume 2 Chapter 10: Experiment</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C10.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="SC - Volume 2 Chapter 10: Experiment" /><published>2023-09-08T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C10</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C10.html"><![CDATA[<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter"><a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C9.html">Previous Chapter</a> | <a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C11.html">Next Chapter</a></h5>

<p>Tl: Sam</p>

<p>…</p>

<p>　—-Time goes back a bit.</p>

<p>　That day I was thinking about something.</p>

<p>　It was about the concept of 『level』 in this world.</p>

<p>　The magic 《Level Seeing》, which allows you to check the level of your opponent. When I used this on people in this world, it would normally activate and I could check their level.
<!--more--></p>

<p>　The average level of a child was about level 1 or 2, and the average level of an adult was about 4 to 7.</p>

<p>　It is imaginable that these levels would naturally increase as they grow up.</p>

<p>　Then, will the level go up by defeating monsters like in “Seven Knights Online”?</p>

<p>　If so, it will be easier to make strong friends. I really wanted to research that.</p>

<p>“Aa!　My Lord!　I am honored to meet you!”</p>

<p>　As I was walking through the village, I was suddenly approached by a man.</p>

<p>　I looked and there was a young man with blond hair.</p>

<p>　His name is Marcus. He is the priest whom I saved from slavery the other day.</p>

<p>　I told him to go back to his hometown, but he was a strange priest who did not stay in one city but traveled around and proselytized.</p>

<p>　This priest, who was convinced that I was a god, said he would stay in the village of Jimari.</p>

<p>　Whenever he meets me, he prays with a noisy intensity. To be honest, it annoys me, but I can’t afford to be too harsh with him, so I put up with it.</p>

<p>“My Lord Dyle-sama. You seemed to be troubled by something, …… what is it?”</p>

<p>“……you’re surprisingly perceptive.”</p>

<p>　Marcus has a nice face and is very attentive. He is the type that seems to be popular with women.</p>

<p>　Hmm, this guy always seems to have some free time, so it might be a good idea to ask him to join me in my experiments. This guy’s conscience won’t hurt even if he does some wild experiments.</p>

<p>“Marcus, do you have time for a little help?”</p>

<p>“Of course, my Lord!　I, Marcus, am willing to go through any ordeal!</p>

<p>　Marcus replied with an exaggerated gesture.</p>

<p>　I’ve got your word. I’ll let you go along with me as long as you like.</p>

<p>“All right, then, let’s head for the woods. Follow me.”</p>

<p>“As you wish!”</p>

<p>　And so I set out with my noisy collaborator.</p>

<p>◇　◇　◇</p>

<p>　I came with Marcus to the forest of Ylde.</p>

<p>　It was the first place I visited when I came to this world, and the place where I met Shea.</p>

<p>　It’s a big place and not many people come here, so it’s a good place to do some experiments.</p>

<p>“I was wondering if you had any idea what you were doing when you heard the word “level”? Does the word ‘level’ mean anything to you?”</p>

<p>“Level ……?　I’m sorry, this Marcus doesn’t sound familiar…….　</p>

<p>Oh, I hate my poor, inadequate head!　Please punish me!”</p>

<p>“No, if you don’t know, that’s okay, I won’t bother punishing you for it.”</p>

<p>“Aah!　How generous of you!”</p>

<p>　Don’t get offended by all this noise.</p>

<p>　Let’s get on with the story.</p>

<p>“Have you ever heard of people getting stronger by defeating monsters?”</p>

<p>“Yes, it is our common knowledge that those who fight monsters generally get stronger faster. It is said that the life force of the monster flows into the person who defeats the monster.”</p>

<p>“I see.”</p>

<p>　Is that how experience is treated in this world?</p>

<p>　In that case, it seems like you can become stronger using the same method as in Seven Knights Online.</p>

<p>Marcus. I’m going to experimentally make you stronger now. Is that alright with you?</p>

<p>“Of course, my Lord. Since the day I became a priest, I have dedicated myself to God.”</p>

<p>　I think I’m a different God than the one he believes in, but …… that’s okay.</p>

<p>　I quickly offered Marcus a certain ring to experiment with.</p>

<p>“Please put this on first.”</p>

<p>“As you wish.”</p>

<p>　Marcus put on the ring without any hesitation.</p>

<p>　He put on the item called 《Party Ring》. The person who puts it on is forced to join the same party as the person who made the ring. Of course, the party will be dissolved if the distance is too great.</p>

<p>　Those in the same party share experience.</p>

<p>　In other words, if the effect of this ring is active, when I kill a monster, Marcus also receives experience.</p>

<p>　Incidentally, in Seven Knights Online, you could easily form a party by using the party function on the console or by becoming a member of the same guild.</p>

<p>　However, in this world, there is no “Party” item on the 《Console》 control panel. And since I didn’t want Marcus to join the guild, the only way left was to use the 《Party Ring》.</p>

<p>“Appraisal 《Level Seeing》”</p>

<p>　Marcus’ level was currently 7. He was one of the strongest among humans.</p>

<p>　Having memorized this, I next took out a certain item.</p>

<p>　The item was in the shape of a small ball, and its name was “Capture Ball,” which is a pretty close call. (Tl: To getting a copyright claim from a cerain company)</p>

<p>　When I activate it, a monster pops out from inside.</p>

<p>『Burrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!』</p>

<p>　The one that jumped out was the bull-shaped monster 『Giant Bull』. It’s a level 10 monster that appears in Seven Knights Online.</p>

<p>　When I had tried to breed it in the game before, I had caught it and sealed it in an item. But I had forgotten about it and had put it in the back of my item box.</p>

<p>　It’s not a rare monster, so I can use it for experiments.</p>

<p>“What?　A monster suddenly appeared!”</p>

<p>“Stay back, Marcus.”</p>

<p>　I let the flustered Marcus back up, and I activated my magic.</p>

<p>“《Slash!》”</p>

<p>　With a snap of my fingers, the magical blade sparkled and sliced through the Giant Bull’s body.</p>

<p>　The level 10 Giant Bull couldn’t withstand it, and it collapsed to the ground.</p>

<p>　I hadn’t tried it before, but I guess the creatures from “Seven Knights Online” also become corpses when they die. In the game, dead monsters immediately turned into drop items.</p>

<p>　In this world, if you want materials, you have to dismantle them properly. I’m used to Seven Knights Online, so it’s a bit of a hassle for me.</p>

<p>“Bi, I’m surprised …… what was that ……?”</p>

<p>“The current monster is the one I summoned. Besides, Marcus, have you noticed any changes in your body?”</p>

<p>“Changes?”</p>

<p>　Marcus looked at his own body with a puzzled look on his face.</p>

<p>　Did I fail?</p>

<p>“I’m sorry, I don’t feel any change in my body,”</p>

<p>“Hmmm. The most important thing to remember is that the information is not the same as the original information. Appraisal 《Level Seeing》.”</p>

<p>　I checked Marcus’ level again.</p>

<p>　His level was 8. His level had increased by one since before he defeated Giant Bull.</p>

<p>“I wonder if I would feel any change if his level had gone up by just one. Would he be able to feel the change if his level were to increase by 10 or so at once?”</p>

<p>　It is necessary to verify this.</p>

<p>　However, it was necessary to carefully choose the person with whom to verify this. The person who verifies it might betray me.</p>

<p>　If he got to level 100, there is a possibility that he could kill me. I have a revive item, but I don’t know if it will work in this world.</p>

<p>　I could try to test it on someone over here, but even if it works on someone over here, whether it will work on me as well is another story.</p>

<p>　If I die, it’s the end.</p>

<p>　I think it’s better to act with that in mind.</p>

<p>“Thank you, Marcus. Now that today’s experiment is over, can I have my ring back?”</p>

<p>“……Yes, sir. Please feel free to contact me anytime.”</p>

<p>　He seemed to be wondering what kind of experiment I was doing, but after returning the ring to me, Marcus left without asking me any questions.</p>

<p>　It’s not that I think he’s going to betray me, but if I give him knowledge, there’s a chance that he’ll do something terrible later on. Whether it is power or knowledge, you should choose who you give it to carefully.</p>

<p>“Now, who should I try it on? ……”</p>

<p>　I returned to the village, pondering.</p>

<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter-1"><a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C9.html">Previous Chapter</a> | <a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C11.html">Next Chapter</a></h5>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="silver castle" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previous Chapter | Next Chapter Tl: Sam … 　—-Time goes back a bit. 　That day I was thinking about something. 　It was about the concept of 『level』 in this world. 　The magic 《Level Seeing》, which allows you to check the level of your opponent. When I used this on people in this world, it would normally activate and I could check their level.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">SC - Volume 2 Chapter 9: Triumphant Return</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C9.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="SC - Volume 2 Chapter 9: Triumphant Return" /><published>2023-09-08T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C9</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C9.html"><![CDATA[<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter"><a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C8.html">Previous Chapter</a> | <a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C10.html">Next Chapter</a></h5>

<p>Tl: Sam</p>

<p>…</p>

<p>　After defeating the bandits in the cave and saving the people who were being held captive, I returned to the Jimari village.</p>

<p>　I could have returned home immediately by riding the angel I summoned, but the captives, especially the priest, refused, saying, “ That’s absurd!” I had to walk home.</p>

<p>　Angels are just monsters that I can summon as many as I want, but to the people here, they are sacred beings.</p>

<p>　I should not treat them too carelessly.</p>

<p>“Welcome back, Dyle-sama!”
<!--more--></p>

<p>　Shea was the first to rush up to me.</p>

<p>　The bandits must have come to the village, but they didn’t look particularly tired. I wonder if there weren’t enough of them.</p>

<p>“I’m home, Shea. It looks like you protected the village, great job.”</p>

<p>“Heh heh.”</p>

<p>　When I patted her head, Shea’s face relaxed.</p>

<p>　When I see things like this, I feel like a child. I have to be careful not to do anything too shocking. If she sees blood or something, she’ll probably get hurt.(Tl: She’s actually the devil)</p>

<p>“Well, you know. I have captured the most important of the bandits who came to the village.”</p>

<p>“What?　You did that?”</p>

<p>“Yes, Yes. He is tied up in that warehouse.”</p>

<p>　I didn’t think she had done her job that perfectly.</p>

<p>　I guess it was the right decision to leave it to 《Angel Knight》.</p>

<p>“Hmm… However, I’ve already heard everything I wanted to ask from the other thieves, so I don’t think there’s anything I want to ask now. I’m sorry you went to the trouble of catching him.”</p>

<p>“No, don’t be sorry!　I did it on my own!　…… Well, what do you want me to do then?　Shall I get rid of it?”</p>

<p>“I can’t leave such a dirty thing to Shea. I will give the order from my side.”</p>

<p>　I’m going to give an order to the angel knight who is standing by and have him dispose of the bandit.</p>

<p>　Incidentally, the bandits I brainwashed with Conversion had already been disposed of. There is no mercy for the wicked.</p>

<p>“That’s right. I brought the captured people and the stolen goods from the bandit’s hideout. I’m sorry, but may I ask you to take care of these?”</p>

<p>“Yes, sir!　Of course!　I’m very good at that kind of detail!”</p>

<p>　Shea replied happily.</p>

<p>　The first time I asked her for a favor, I was a little hesitant to do so, but recently I feel that I have lost my hesitation.</p>

<p>“You can use the summoned Angel Knights as you like. Please help me.”</p>

<p>“Yup!　Leave it to me!”</p>

<p>　Shea was full of enthusiasm.</p>

<p>　I’d have to do my best to keep up with her work.</p>

<p>◇　◇　◇</p>

<p>　One week after the bandit trouble.</p>

<p>　Thanks to the efforts of Shea and the other villagers, almost all of those who had been captured were able to return to their former villages.</p>

<p>　The few who hadn’t returned are still in the Jimari village. They don’t want to leave me. I felt sorry for them, so I built them a new house in the village. By the way, the priest was among them, and he worshiped me every time he saw me.</p>

<p>　I am returning stolen goods little by little to their original owners.</p>

<p>　If you go to a village once, you can ask an angel you summoned to take your belongings and it’s not that hard. Recently, it seems that what I have done has begun to spread to neighboring villages, and there are people who come all the way to the village of Jimari to see me.</p>

<p>　I don’t want to be too conspicuous, but Shea is doing a good job of keeping me out of trouble. It’s like she’s my secretary.</p>

<p>　Oh, and one more thing has changed.</p>

<p>　Shea, who had not been talking to many other people her age, has made a friend.</p>

<p>　She made a friend, Luna, a beastman. She was one of the people I rescued from the cave.</p>

<p>　She was living with other beastmen in the forest near the village of Jimari. She often came to the village and talked happily with Shea about something.</p>

<p>　It’s good to have friends. I hope that she will nurture her friendship and make many good memories for me.</p>

<p>　Well, things were hectic but peaceful these days.</p>

<p>　Just as I was thinking that it was time to start doing something to fix the castle, Luna, who was visiting the village, asked me for a favor.</p>

<p>“Dyle-sama. Actually, there is something I need your help with…….”</p>

<p>　Luna began using an unfamiliar honorific.</p>

<p>　Her face was dark. Is it something serious?</p>

<p>“What’s going on?”</p>

<p>“Orcs have been appearing near my village recently. But my people are no match for them, and if we don’t do something about it, we will be killed one day…….”</p>

<p>　The orcs are pig-headed subhumans, as I recall. they also appeared in Seven Knights Online.</p>

<p>　Although it moved slowly, it was a troublesome monster with high strength and stamina.</p>

<p>　It didn’t drop very good items, and it wasn’t a monster I would actively hunt.</p>

<p>　However, if they came close to where you live, there is no way to avoid them. This was a serious problem.</p>

<p>　I asked Shea, who was standing nearby.</p>

<p>“Shea, how many days do you think you can stay away from the village?”</p>

<p>“About three days is no problem. I can accompany you for that period of time!”</p>

<p>　Shea replied in no time. She is a very capable girl, as always.</p>

<p>“I see, it’s perfect if Shea can come too. I have some things I want to try, so let’s go to the village of Luna.”</p>

<p>“…… eh!　Dyle-sama is coming?”</p>

<p>“I’m sure he will. It’s only natural to help out a friend in need.”</p>

<p>　I patted Luna’s fluffy head.</p>

<p>　Luna’s tail wagged in delight. She was shy and didn’t show it in words or facial expressions, but she was still a child when she showed it in this kind of situation.</p>

<p>　…..I feel like Shea was looking at me in a scary way, but I thought it was just my imagination.</p>

<p>“By the way, Dyle-sama, what is it that you want to try?”</p>

<p>　I stopped stroking her and she asked me curiously.</p>

<p>　I hadn’t told her about this yet, come to think of it.</p>

<p>“Even with the angels I summon, there is still a lack of strength. That’s what I think.”</p>

<p>“I see. ……. I do not think there is any problem with the current situation, but if Dyle-sama says so, then there must be no doubt about it.”</p>

<p>　Certainly, as Shea said, if you look at it from a general perspective, the strength of this village is not a problem.</p>

<p>　Since we summon various kinds of angels every day, we usually see them in the village. Even if we fought a big country, we have the strength here that we would not be defeated so easily.</p>

<p>　But what if a player came from Seven Knights Online?</p>

<p>　I doubt if I and my summoned angels would be enough to win. Even if we could win, I don’t have confidence in my ability to protect people over here like Shea and Luna.</p>

<p>“I thought about it. How can I protect the people of this village? And I came to a conclusion.”</p>

<p>　Shea and Luna gulped when they heard these words.</p>

<p>　Both of them are curious. After I had made a big show of it, I said those words.</p>

<p>“It’s time for leveling.”</p>

<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter-1"><a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C8.html">Previous Chapter</a> | <a href="/silver%20castle/Silver-Castle-V2C10.html">Next Chapter</a></h5>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="silver castle" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previous Chapter | Next Chapter Tl: Sam … 　After defeating the bandits in the cave and saving the people who were being held captive, I returned to the Jimari village. 　I could have returned home immediately by riding the angel I summoned, but the captives, especially the priest, refused, saying, “ That’s absurd!” I had to walk home. 　Angels are just monsters that I can summon as many as I want, but to the people here, they are sacred beings. 　I should not treat them too carelessly. “Welcome back, Dyle-sama!”]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BG - Volume 6 Chapter 5: Tanaka Signs</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C5.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BG - Volume 6 Chapter 5: Tanaka Signs" /><published>2023-09-05T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2023-09-05T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C5</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C5.html"><![CDATA[<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter"><a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C4.html">Previous Chapter</a> | <a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C6.html">Next Chapter</a></h5>

<p>Tl: Sam</p>

<p>…</p>

<p>“If the amount is correct, please sign your signature. Or is there something wrong with ……?” <br />
“No, no. No, no, this is fine. I’ll sign it.”</p>

<p>　I can’t complain about this. <br />
　There was nothing against me in the document, so I had no problem with it.</p>

<p>　I signed in three places and stamped my seal. Then I noticed a piece of paper that looked like colored paper in the document.
<!--more--></p>

<p>“Hm?　This is…….” <br />
“Oh, um. If you don’t mind, would you mind signing it personally ……?”</p>

<p>　When I looked at Hazuki-san’s face, it was bright red. <br />
　She didn’t look like the type of person who would mix public and private matters, but she wanted my autograph that badly?　Hmmm, I wonder.</p>

<p>　I didn’t know if my autograph was worth it, but I had to respond to his request.</p>

<p>“Your autograph, yes, that’s fine.” <br />
“Really?　Thank you!”</p>

<p>　Hazuki-san was delighted with a big smile on his face. <br />
　If she’s this happy with just an autograph, it’s worth writing.</p>

<p>　I wrote the signature I had secretly practiced on the colored paper. Then Riri jumped out of my breast pocket and landed next to the paper.</p>

<p>“Riri!” <br />
“Hm?　What’s wrong, Riri?”</p>

<p>　Riri began tugging at the pen I was holding. <br />
　Maybe Riri wants to write, too?　But Riri is too small to hold a pen, and as I was thinking about that…… my eyes fell on a red ink pad for seals.</p>

<p>“This would work for Riri, too.”</p>

<p>　I grabbed Riri’s hand and let her place her fingertip on the red ink. <br />
　Then I place Riri’s reddened hand on the colored paper. Riri’s handprint was left on the paper.</p>

<p>“I guess even Riri can sign this.” <br />
“Riri!”(Tl: She sounds so proud of herself)</p>

<p>　Riri happily flicked her handprint to the edge of the paper. <br />
　I’m glad she’s satisfied with it,……, I thought, but then I thought about it and realized that it might be a nuisance for Hazuki to have to deal with. I thought about it and suggested to her that I would write her signature on the other colored papers as well,</p>

<p>“Well, I never thought that even Riri would sign my autograph!　I am too happy!　I’m going to keep this color paper as a family heirloom!”</p>

<p>　Hazuki was sobbing with joy. <br />
　I was a little taken back by how happy she was. Riri also seemed to have no idea what was going on and tilted her head. You’d never think she’d be moved by her own handprints.</p>

<p>“Hey! I heard a loud voice, but what’s wrong…? Why are you crying!?”</p>

<p>　It was a man in a suit who came in saying that. <br />
　He was about 50 years old. He looked like Hazuki-san’s boss.</p>

<p>“I was so happy when I got this.” <br />
“Oh, I see. You were a fan…… what are you doing getting autographs?　Get to work!”</p>

<p>　The boss was pushed by Hazuki at first, but then scolded her.
　Well, of course. That’s how I would normally react.</p>

<p>　But she’s crying right now, so I had to follow up.</p>

<p>“Well, I don’t mind signing autographs, so please don’t be so angry with her. If there is someone else who wants it, I’ll write as many as you want.” <br />
“No, that’s not what I’m saying, but …… no. Ummm …….”</p>

<p>　The boss suddenly thought about it. <br />
　I wonder what’s wrong.(Tl: Lol big boss wants a copy)</p>

<p>“Well, um, I’m sorry, but could you please sign it for me too?　My grandchildren are big fans of yours, Tanaka-sama.”</p>

<p>　Boss-san lowered his eyebrows and asked me to sign his autograph. I had no idea that he would actually ask me for an additional autograph. <br />
　I said, “Yes, yes”. I was a little confused, but picked up an autograph pen. Then, as I was writing my signature to my boss, other staff members, who must have heard the rumor, started to come over to me.</p>

<p>“I’ve always had a crush on Shachiken…….” <br />
“I love Shachiken!　I watch all your videos!” <br />
“I’m a member of his fan club!” <br />
“My child is a fan of Shachiken…….”</p>

<p>　The stacks of colored papers were piling up in front of me. Apparently, when the staff members found out I was here, they bought some papers in the hope of getting my autograph. <br />
　Riri thought she was being told she could play with them, and she was flipping through the bills before I could.</p>

<p>　I had no choice. …… Riri was keen on the idea, and we were on time, so I decided to go along with her.</p>

<p>“I understand. But I would appreciate it if you could give me one for each person.” <br />
“”””””””"”Thank you! “”””””””””</p>

<p>　A number of heads were neatly lowered. <br />
　In the end, I signed for almost all of the staff together with Riri.</p>

<p>….</p>

<p>Tl Note: Riri Is da real MVP lol. Have a chemistry exam, but I’m not particularly bothered, so I’m putting out some content</p>

<h5 id="previous-chapter--next-chapter-1"><a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C4.html">Previous Chapter</a> | <a href="/black%20guild/Black-Guild-V6C6.html">Next Chapter</a></h5>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="black guild" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previous Chapter | Next Chapter Tl: Sam … “If the amount is correct, please sign your signature. Or is there something wrong with ……?” “No, no. No, no, this is fine. I’ll sign it.” 　I can’t complain about this. 　There was nothing against me in the document, so I had no problem with it. 　I signed in three places and stamped my seal. Then I noticed a piece of paper that looked like colored paper in the document.]]></summary></entry></feed>